Edilson Domingues Junior

34 Anos Single Curitiba - PR

Contacts: (41) 98406-2938 linkedin.com/in/edilsondjr edilsondjr@gmail.com

Professional Profile

Analytic, self-taught, and proactive professional. I am constantly improving my knowledge and my skills, and right now I am focused mainly on cloud technology, DevOps culture, as well as tools for maintenance.

Graduated in Computer Network Technology, and post-graduate in Network & Telecom. I have experience working with Windows Server, PowerShell, Linux, Firewall (PfSense), DHCP, DNS, Web Server (Apache2), VPN (Open VPN), WSUS, WDS, MDT, Active Directory (includes GPO), and virtualization on Hyper-V and VMware.

Also, I have knowledge of Python, Flask, MySQL, SQL Server, Shell Script, PowerShell, Git, Sourcetree, Jenkins, Vagrant, Ansible, Puppet, Docker, Docker Swarm, ELK Stack, Office 365, Azure (Virtual Machines), and AWS (EC2, VPC, Auto Scaling, RDS, S3, ECS/ECR, CloudFront, and Route 53).

Education

DevOps Engineer
Online Course on Alura – Sep 2018 to Oct 2018
Estimated Duration: 130hrs;

Post-Graduation: Network and Telecom Specialization – Pontifícia Universidade Católica. Curitiba/PR. 2017;

Computer Network Technology – Faculdades Santa Cruz. Curitiba/PR. 2014.

Certifications

MTA: Cloud Fundamentals 2018 – Feb 2018; MCSA: Windows Server 2016 – Aug 2018.

Languages

Portuguese: Native Language;

English: Advanced.

Professional Experience

Assembleia Legislativa do Estado do Paraná

Infrastructure Analyst Oct 2013 – Present

- Provide support to help desk, development and ERP management teams;
- Manage Windows Server and Linux on-premises;

- Hyper-V e VMware Vsphere virtualization;
- PowerShell Scripting;
- Some services managed are: AD DS, DNS, DHCP, WSUS, WDS, MDT.

Metal Typo

IT Supervisor

Jan 2013 – Aug 2013

- Head of a small IT department;
- ERP Totvs Protheus general management;
- Install, configure and maintain servers like Microsoft Windows Server 2008R2, Microsoft SQL Server 2008R2/2012, and Debian Linux servers;

<u>Ibratec</u>

IT Assistant

Apr 2010 – Sep 2012

- Desktop, Notebook, Servers and network maintenance;
- Internal customer support (Windows, Internet, and Office Suite)